autoclubrevolution.com 2019-11-28

# Privacy Policy - Auto Club Revolution | #1️⃣ in Gaming, Movies, TV, Sport and Comics

## Privacy Policy And Consent To Use Of Data

### IMPORTANT: BY SUBMITTING DATA TO US AND/OR USING THE AUTO CLUB REVOLUTION WEB SITE YOU GIVE YOUR CONSENT THAT ALL PERSONAL DATA THAT YOU SUBMIT MAY BE PROCESSED BY US IN THE MANNER AND FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY.

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes Eutechnyx’s current policies and practices with regard to Personal Data collected by Eutechnyx manually or through all of Eutechnyx web sites (the “Web Site”). The term “Personal Data” refers to any information which identifies you as an individual such as your name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address. (as further defined in Data Protection Act 1998).

### Notification of changes to this Policy

We are continually improving and adding new functionality and features to this Web Site and improving and adding to our existing products, services and events. Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law and the changing nature of technology, our data practices will change from time to time. If and when our data practices change, we will (as soon as reasonably practicable) post the changes on our Web Site to notify you of the changes. We encourage you to check this page frequently.

### Collection of Personal Data including e-mail addresses

We collect the information you give us when you use our Web Site. Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, email address, phone number, home address, birth date, and credit card information.

You may use our Web Site to contact us and if you do so we will ask for your name and e-mail address. This information will only be used to respond to your query and will, provided we do not have any need to retain the information for any other legitimate purpose, be deleted as soon as we have dealt with your query.

We sometimes supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For instance, if inaccurate postal or zip codes are received, we will use third party software to fix them.

### Use of Personal Data

We process your Personal Data only for specific and limited purposes including to complete your purchases and orders. We ask only for data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes. When we ask you for Personal Data, we tell you the purposes for which we will process that data. In addition to the above we may use your Personal Data to:

  * contact you occasionally to inform you of new services we will be providing, or events or articles we think will be of interest to you.
  * send you regular updates by e-mail or by post on client seminars or related events.
  * send you requested information and promotional material.
  * use your Personal Data for marketing purposes and market research.
  * use your Personal Data internally to help us improve our services and to help resolve any problems.

Each mailing we send to you will contain instructions on how you can opt-out of receiving any further mailings from us. We will not contact you by e-mail unless you have expressly requested us to do so or you are an existing customer and we have received your contact details in the course of selling to you or negotiating with you for the sale of products or services.

### Opt-out choice

If you do not wish to receive information from us and want to be removed from our standard mailing list, please e-mail us at info@eutechnyx.com. We will reply by e-mail to confirm that your details have been removed or, if that is not possible, the reasons for not doing so. It may not always be possible for us to completely remove your details from our system as to do so may render us in breach of data protection law and guidelines. Your details will however be suppressed and you will receive no further mailings from us.

### Anonymous data collected through this Web Site

In addition to the information we collect as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our Web Site. For example, we use technology to track which pages of our Web Site our visitors view. We also use technology to determine which Web browsers our visitors use. This technology does not identify you personally, it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our Web Site.

Our Web Site contains hyperlinks to other pages on our Web Site. We use technology to track how often these links are used and which pages on our Web Site our visitors choose to view. Again this technology does not identify you personally – it simply enables us to compile statistics about the use of these hyperlinks.

We use this anonymous data to improve the content and functionality of this Web Site and our e-mail updates, to better understand our customers and markets, and to improve our products and services, and as further set out below.

We will never share your personal information with third parties without your consent. We may, however, share anonymous, non-personal, aggregated and/or public information with third parties.

### Cookies

In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may use temporary “cookies” that collect your IP address and the date and time you accessed this Web Site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. You can also set your browser to refuse to accept cookies though most are initially set to accept cookies. If you set your browser to refuse cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all parts of this Web Site. If you do not set your browser to refuse cookies it is implied that you consent to their use. For more information about cookies and how to disable them please go do www.allaboutcookies.org.

We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as determining how many of our visitors are from outside of the UK.

We may also perform IP lookups to determine which domain you are coming from (i.e: aol.com, yourcompany.com) to more accurately gauge our users’ demographics.

### Disclosure of your Personal Data

We do not share, sell or distribute your Personal Data with unrelated third parties, except under these limited circumstances:-

  * Personal Data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for us for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. For example, sometimes a third party may have access to your Personal Data in order to handle our mailings on our behalf.
  * We may share or transfer the information in our databases to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this Web Site, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganisation, dissolution or similar event.
  * We may share or transfer the information in our databases for marketing purposes with our publishers, some of whom may be situated outside the European Economic Area and we refer you to our policy on transfer of data abroad set out below.

Where appropriate, before disclosing Personal Data to a third party, we contractually require the third party to take adequate precautions to protect that data.

### PLEASE BE AWARE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY BE AMENDED BY THE TERMS OF SERVICE RELATING TO PARTICULAR EUTECHNYX TITLES AND GAMES AND YOU SHOULD REFER TO THOSE TERMS OF SERVICE FOR ANY SUCH AMENDMENTS WHICH WILL BE DETAILED THEREIN.

### Data Integrity and Security

We strive to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of Personal Data in our databases and to protect the privacy and security of our databases. We keep your Personal Data only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or document retention requirements.

Our servers and our databases are protected by industry standard security technology, such as industry standard firewalls and password protection.

Sometimes we process Sensitive Personal Data (as defined in the Data Protection Act) that requires industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted browsers. We use 128-bit encryption, the most powerful available, to protect transmissions when we send such information over the Internet.

The employees who have access to Personal Data have been trained to handle such data properly and in accordance with our security protocols and strict standards of confidentiality.

### Data Access and Corrections

Upon receipt of your written request and enough information to permit us to identify your Personal Data, we will disclose to you the Personal Data we hold about you. We will also correct, amend or delete any Personal Data that is inaccurate and notify any third party recipients of the necessary changes.

If you wish to access or correct your Personal Data, please write to our data protection officer Darren Jobling at Eutechnyx or e-mail us at info@eutechnyx.com We do not charge for complying with a correction request, however, for all other requests, we may charge a small fee to cover our costs. Requests to delete Personal Data are subject to any applicable legal and ethical reporting or document retention obligations imposed on us.

### Link to other web sites

This Web Site contains hyperlinks to web sites that are not operated by us. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party web sites or any association with their operators. We do not control these web sites and are not responsible for their data or privacy practices. We urge you to review any privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any Personal Data about yourself.

### Transfer of Data Abroad

We may, from time to time, transfer your Personal Data outside the European Economic Area for example to our publishers who have offices outside the EEA. If the level of privacy protection in any such a country does not comply with recognised international standards, we will ensure that data transferred are adequately protected and that the transfer of data to third parties in such countries is made pursuant to a contract or other measures providing adequate protection.

Of course, the Internet is made up of a large number of international connections. If you are visiting this Web Site from a country other than the country in which our server is located, the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this Web Site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to these transfers.

### Governing Law

This privacy policy forms part of our Web Site Terms of Use (CLICK HERE TO ACCESS OUR TERMS OF USE) and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England. You agree to submit any dispute arising out of your use of this Web Site to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales.

### Data Protection Register

Eutechnyx Limited has notified the Information Commissioner of its data processing activities. Its registration number is Z6097647.

### Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process your Personal Data, please contact us by e-mailing us at info@eutechnyx.com.
